everycircuit.com 2018-09-30

# EveryCircuit

We understand the circuits published through use of our Service (âContentâ) could contain private information, and we take the responsibility of protecting the confidentiality of your content very seriously. In addition, we also collect and use various types of personal, confidential information you supply to us in order to use our Service (the âServiceâ). We have established this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect and use your sensitive information, and your ability to correct or modify the information you have provided to us. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [legal@musemaze.com](mailto:legal@musemaze.com). We welcome your thought and comments, working to improve our policy to meet the needs of our members. By using our Service, you accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. 

Your content

At MuseMaze, one of our guiding principles is that each of our registered memberâs private content belongs solely to that member. Your private content does not belong to us. We will never assert any claims of ownership over your private content. However, if you publish your content to the public, we may use that content. 

Registration

In order to use the Service that MuseMaze offers, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you will be required to provide some information, which includes your username, e-mail address, password and profession. This information is used to provide you with important services such as automated updates through e-mail. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your username and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. 

Information collection and use

Other than the circuits, the information we collect from you generally can be divided into three categories: (1) personally identifiable information; (2) generic and aggregated information; and (3) log data. How we collect and use each type of information is described below. Our primary goals in collecting this information are to improve our Service, to administer your account (if applicable), and to enable our members to enjoy and easily navigate our Service. These activities, together with the storage of circuits for our registered members, are collectively referred to below as the âService.â 

__Personally identifiable information:__ If you choose to become a registered user or member of our Service, we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you, and is referred to below as âPersonal Information.â Personal Information includes, but is not limited to email address. Also included within the scope of Personal Information are a registered memberâs private circuits. 

We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non-Identifying Information) mainly to operate the Service and to respond to your inquiries. We may also use your Personal Information to contact you with our newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. 

Finally, please note that your Personal Information may contain certain elements (such as your profession) that, when taken alone or when aggregated with information we receive from other users, no longer identifies you. See âGeneric and Aggregated Informationâ below for other ways in which these elements may be used. 

__Generic and aggregated information:__ We may collect non-personally-identifying information about you as part of your registration for, or personalization or use of, our Service. This information may include, for example, your individual Service preferences. In addition, we may extract non-personally-identifying elements from certain Personal Information you provide (for example, the profession). We will never extract private circuits and designate them as Generic or Aggregated Information. Finally, we may combine and aggregate any information we receive from you (including Personal Information but excluding private circuits) with information received from other users of our Service in order to obtain demographic and other statistical information that no longer identifies or pertains specifically to any particular user or member. When stored, used, and/or disclosed separately from any data that could, in combination, allow others to contact or identify you, all of the information described in this paragraph is considered âGeneric Information.â 

We may use Generic Information on its own or in combination with your Personal Information and/or data in order to provide you with tailored and relevant Services, and to analyze and understand how our Service is used. We may also use Generic Information (particularly including aggregated, non-identifying statistical data) in order to provide our members and others with reports and other materials regarding business trends and general information pertaining to the use of our Service. 

__Log data:__ Our servers automatically record certain information whenever you use our Service. This information is called log data. Log data may include information such as your computerâs Internet address, device type, circuits accessed through the use of our Service, the time spent on those circuits, information you search for, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor, analyze the use of, and administer the Service, as well as to increase the functionality, user-friendliness, and relevance of the Service. We also use this information to verify that the users of our Service meet the criteria required to process their requests. Log data may also be aggregated and used as described under âGeneric and Aggregated Informationâ above. 

Information sharing and disclosure

__Payment and service providers.__ We may employ third parties to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform services such as maintenance, database management, analytics and improvement of the features offered by our Service as well as to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties may have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. 

__Third party marketing.__ We do not share your Personal Information with third parties for marketing purposes. 

__Data storage.__ The electronic storage of your Content requires a significant amount of memory. As such, we contract with third party service providers to store this Content. Although we have agreements in place with those service providers that prohibit them from sharing or distributing Content to third parties, there is always a possibility that a problem could occur (e.g., they experience a breach of security) and that your Content could be disseminated. 

__Aggregate information and non-identifying information.__ We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes, though we will never share your Content for such purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information. 

__Compliance with laws and law enforcement.__ If we are required to disclose Personal Information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, in response to law enforcement inquiry or in compliance with applicable laws, we will make such disclosure. 

__Change in ownership.__ We will not sell (or trade or rent) Personal Information to other companies as part of our regular course of business. However, it's possible that we may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. If that happens, your Personal Information may be disclosed to another company, but that disclosure will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect. 

Security and storage of information

We are very concerned with safeguarding your personal information and Content. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. When you are asked to enter sensitive information (such as your password), that information is encrypted and is protected with what we think is the best encryption software currently available in the industry - Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL"). We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online, and we also take several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. Finally, we rely on third-party service providers for the physical security of some of our computer hardware. While we believe our security procedures are adequate, as are those of our third party service providers, we cannot guarantee complete security. 100% complete security does not presently exist anywhere online or offline. 

Your information may be transferred toâand maintained onâcomputers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, we will transfer your Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

Links to other sites

Our Service may contain links to other websites (including but not limited to banner ads and other advertisements). We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites, and our linking to these websites may not be construed as any type of endorsement of such websites or any affiliation with their providers. These other websites may place cookies or other files on your computer, collect data, and/or solicit personal information from you. You must check the privacy statements of these other websites to understand their policies for collecting and using such information. 

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [legal@musemaze.com](mailto:legal@musemaze.com). 

Updates to this policy

If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on the Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. Changes may be retroactive. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us at [legal@musemaze.com](mailto:legal@musemaze.com). This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 1st, 2018.
